# **Daniella Potts**

# WEB DEVELOPER

I am a dedicated developer with a passion for creating seamless websites and games, and am constantly striving to learn new technologies. My expertise lies in developing intuitive and aesthetic interfaces, and engaging web applications that prioritize accessibility and a clean codebase.

Llandudno, United Kingdom contact@DaniellaJPotts.com (+##) #### ######

linkedin.com/in/DaniellaJPotts github.com/DaniellaJPotts github.com/cathrtic-tv



# EXPERIENCES

#### Front-end Developer, Probit (prev. Probit Consulting)

Gaerwen, United Kingdom • Hybrid

10/2022 - 08/2024

- At Probit, I developed Asset Investment Manager 5 (AIM 5), a .NET webapp, and made multiple compatibility and maintenance updates to AIM 4.
- Made designs and design decisions, and worked closely with a professional designer, to redesign and enhance the user interface and experience.
- Implemented several refactor improvements, including migrating the styling and custom preprocessor from Less to SCSS.
- · Pushed for and added accessibility standards, following WCAG, to ensure a more inclusive user experience and ease-of-use.

### [ Voluntary ] Community Playtester, Embark Studios

Stockholm, Sweden • Remote

- Participate in closed playtesting sessions where I talk to devs, and provide valuable feedback to improve the game mechanics, balancing, first impressions, and overall user experience for THE FINALS and ARC Raiders.
- Frequently report bugs with reproduction steps to staff, and other issues found on their media posts.

### [ Voluntary ] Solo Full-Stack, Great Orme Exploration Society Llandudno, United Kingdom

01/2021 - Present

- · Designed, developed, and implemented the website for members of the Great Orme Exploration Society (GOES).
- . Maintain regular updates to the site, whilst currently re-developing in Laravel, with plans to add admin and user accounts, and a fresh design.
- This site is currently using vanilla PHP, SCSS, and JavaScript.

# PROJECTS

#### The CathRTic Archives

09/2024 - Present

• Upload to the YouTube channel "CathRTic Archive", which archives videos and otherwise "lost media", for THE FINALS and ARC Raiders.

## **CathRTic Web Mirrors**

07/2024 - Present

· Maintain and developed a website mirror-maker. And, host various copies of Embark Studios' sites, including their game wikis and spin-off sites.

# EDUCATION

### **BSc (Hons) Computer Science, First-Class Honours**

**Bangor University, United Kingdom** 

- Completed modules including, Advanced Game Development, Software Engineering, Web Development, and User Experience (UX) & HCI.
- Created the dissertation, "A Tool to Procedurally Generate Photorealistic Terrain using Unity". This used a variety of researched techniques including, coherent random noise, and erosion simulation.

# 🔀 SKILLS

#### Languages

PHP HTML CSS SCSS Less JavaScript TypeScript C# Python Lua

#### **Technologies**

ASP.NET Laravel npm Vite Vue.js Unity GitHub Actions

## Other Technologies

Figma DaVinci Resolve

# INTERESTS



